Donald W. Furler collection of railroad photographs
Center for Railroad Photography & Art
- 1932-1954, Furler-24; 516 images (Binder Binder 24, Pages 001-131)
  Alton and Southern Railway Company; Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway; Atlantic and North Carolina Railroad; Baltimore and Ohio Railroad; Canadian National Railway; Canadian Pacific Railway; Central Railroad of New Jersey; Central Vermont Railroad; Chesapeake and Ohio Railway; Chicago and North Western Transportation Company; Chicago and Southern Railroad; Chicago and Western Indiana Railroad; Chicago, Burlington and Quincy Railroad; Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul and Pacific Railroad (Milwaukee Road); Chronister Lumber Company; Cleveland, Cincinnati, Chicago and St. Louis Railway; Dansville and Mount Morris Railroad; Delaware and Hudson Railway; Delaware, Lackawanna and Western Railroad; Erie Lackawanna Railway; Erie Railroad; Franklin and Carolina Railroad (Camp Manufacturing Company); Gifford-Hill and Company; Grand Trunk Railway; Illinois Central Railroad; Ironton Railroad; Lehigh and Hudson River Railway; Lehigh Valley Railroad; Lehigh Valley Transit Company; Maine Central Railroad Company; Maryland and Pennsylvania Railroad; Medusa Portland Cement Company; Minnesota Transfer Railway; Missouri Pacific Railroad; Missouri-Kansas-Texas Railroad; Mobile and Ohio Railroad; Morristown and Erie Railway; Newburgh and South Shore Railroad; New York Central Railroad; New York, Chicago and St. Louis Railroad (Nickel Plate Road); New York, Ontario and Western Railway; Pennsylvania Railroad; Pittsburg, Shawmut and Northern Railroad; Reading Railroad; Rutland Railroad; Seaboard Air Line Railroad; Southern Pacific Transportation Company; Southern Railway; St. Louis and O'Fallon Railway Company; St. Louis-San Francisco Railway (Frisco Lines); St. Louis Southwestern Railway; Texas and Pacific Railway; Toledo, Peoria and Western Railway; Wabash Railroad; Western Maryland Railway
- 1956, Furler-25; 166 images (Binder Binder 25, Pages 001-009)
  Alabama; Maine; Montreal (Canada); New Hampshire; New Jersey; Ontario (Canada); Pennsylvania; Quebec (Canada); Saskatchewan (Canada); Vermont
  Boston Maine Railways; Canadian National Railway; Canadian Pacific Railway; Central Vermont Railroad; Grand Trunk Western Railroad; Maine Central Railroad Company; Mount Washington Cog Railway; Pennsylvania Railroad; Philadelphia Suburban Transportation Company; Quebec Central Railway; Reading Railroad